《始祖家族》前情提要
Previously on "The originals"...
這里曾經是我的家  我要奪回來
This town was my home once. I want it back.
我們的地盤在遭受攻擊
Our community is under attack.
擁有無限力量的復活巫師
Resurrected witches with vast power?
收獲祭
It's the harvest.
四個女孩本應死去再復生
Four girls were meant to die and be reborn.
但有人劫走了那力量
Someone jacked that power.
我相信當你深愛著一個人時
I believe that when you love someone
而那人也同樣愛你
and that person loves you in return,
你會變得格外脆弱
you're uniquely vulnerable.
塞萊斯特  她因我而死
Celeste, she died because of me.
可以的話請叫我的真名
I'd appreciate it if you'd call me by my real name--
塞萊斯特
Celeste.
那海莉呢
What about Hayley?
我的所有背叛對這個家族的傷害
None of my treachery will harm this family
都比不上你對她的感情而帶來的
as much as your feelings for her.
這把刀片現在飽含著
This blade contains
我從吸血鬼身上收獲的力量
all the power I harvested from the vampires.
它能做出比死亡更可怕的事情
It will do things worse than death.
你準備好做出最終的獻祭了嗎
And are you ready for the final offering?
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯 胖兔純  青椒  叉燒包  米蘇
時間軸 大噴子  今  寶寶    后期 漁夫
校對 米蘇   總監 米蘇
救救我
Someone help me.
感謝大家的到來
Thank you all for coming.
最對我來說意義重大
It means more than I can tell you.
今天是教堂重建后
We gather today for the first public service
第一次布道
of our newly reopened church.
圣安妮終于能重新成為我們社區的
St. Anne's can finally once again be the heart
精神寄托
of our community,
將我們大家聚集在一起
where we can congregate as a people united.
此時此刻  我們齊聚與此贊美上帝
Here, this hour, we come together to praise god
給予我們的感恩
and give thanks.
教堂之前發生的事件是一場悲劇
The events that took place at our church were tragic.
有什么問題嗎
Problem?
沒有
No.
那就專心一點
Then pay attention.
要讓人家覺得我們是虔誠的教區居民
We're meant to seem like devoted parishioners.
...正因為我們心中仍存希望
...And it is that hope in our hearts
也因為許多善心人士的慷慨相助
and with the help of many benefactors
我們今天才能再次坐在這里
that allows us to be here today.
因此我們帶著信念聚集于此
So we gather with renewed spirit
更加強大  更加堅定地
made stronger, committed to the ideals
追尋和平與愛  阿門
of peace and love. Amen.
阿門
Amen.
每座墓碑都有人精心打理
Each tomb is well cared for.
家人會在墓碑前擺放各種裝飾
Families honor their dead with displays of affection
-來悼念死者  -有人在外面嗎
- and respect... - Is someone there?
這座墳墓屬于德弗羅家族
This tomb belongs to the Deveraux family,
這個家族向來因與巫術的緊密聯系
Known throughout the quarter for their strong connection
聞名于法屬區
to witchcraft.
求求你幫幫我
Please help me!
如果你仔細查看  這些新砌的磚塊
And if you look close, these fresh bricks
說明家族不久前
tell us someone in the family
才有族人去世
has recently fallen.
那是什么聲音
What is that?
放我出去
Let me out!
你好  莫妮可
Hello, Monique.
歡迎回到這個世界
Welcome back to the land of the living.
始祖家族
第一季  第十三集
斯蒂芬妮·拉沃
生于1914年5月28日  卒于1990年8月7日
費德里克·德弗羅
生于1936年12月24日  卒于1999年6月12日
怎么了  發生了什么事
What is it? What's going on?
奇跡發生了
It's a miracle.
莫妮可
Monique?
今早的布道真不錯  神父
Lovely sermon this morning, father.
非常鼓舞人心
Quite inspirational.
我沒想過你會來參加
I wasn't expecting you to join us.
我們來是想聽聽你對最近的海地入侵
Oh, we were hoping for some word from your human sources
有沒有什么線索
on the recent Haitian invasion.
我的人已經盡力打聽了
My guys have their ears to the ground.
但沒有人聽到任何關于你們說的
And no one has seen or heard any sign
那個人的消息
of whatever his name is.
他被人稱為圖德圣父
He's called Papa Tunde.
如今  他身上聚集著所有
And right now, he's wandering the corridor
我埋在花園的吸血鬼的力量
with the power he absorbed
正在這附近四處游蕩
from every soul I had buried in the garden.
所以或許該讓你的人
So you might want to put your ear
再更加努力一點
a little closer to the ground.
或者  我也可以選擇遠離這場
Or I could steer clear of whatever war is brewing
你們之間一觸即發的戰爭
between your kind and his
在我還沒陷入...
before I find myself in--
祝賀你  教堂又能重新對大家開放了
I wanted to congratulate you on getting the church up and running.
看得出你現在不方便說話
I can see this is a bad time.
很高興見到你  馬塞爾
Nice to see you, Marcel.
卡米
Cami.
別看著我
Well, don't look at me.
我已經試著讓她遠離這里了
I tried to send her away.
迪亞哥  有什么消息嗎
Yes, Diego, what do you have for me?
我們收到了一份禮物
Uh, we got a special delivery.
你能說明白點嗎
Would you care to elaborate?
不知這代表我們的女巫問題已經被解決了
Either our witch problems are over
還是它才剛剛開始
or they're just getting started.
馬塞爾
Marcel.
再見  神父
Father.
上帝與你同在
God be with you.
謝謝  上帝與你同在
Thank you. God be with you.
謝謝  上帝與你...
Thank you. God be with y--
我可不這么想  但還是感謝你的祝福
Oh, I doubt that, but I do appreciate the thought.
巴斯蒂娜
Bastiana.
瘋狂逆轉  靈魂即逝
Torsion fou, mort de l'espirit.
當你在地獄見到你的侄子肖恩時
Give your nephew Sean my regards
替我向他問好
when you see him in hell.
需要什么道具嗎  哥哥
Can I get you anything, brother?
放大鏡  還是煙斗
A magnifying glass, a pipe perhaps?
不如跟大家
You have a theory
說說你的看法如何  尼克勞斯
that you'd like to share with us, Niklaus?
過去那會兒  女巫們要表達威脅時
Back in the day, the witches wanted to send a threat,
她們會殺一只雞然后放在你門口
they'd just kill a chicken and leave it on your doorstep.
那這還真是只巨大兇狠的雞
It's rather a large and ominous chicken,
你說是嗎
wouldn't you say?
圖德圣父輕易制服了麗貝卡
Papa Tunde defeated Rebekah with ease,
還差點也解決了我們倆
almost got the two of us as well.
如果他真是跟女巫們一邊的
If he was supposed to be their prize fighter,
為什么她們要殺死他  還放在我們門口
why leave him for dead in our front yard?
看上去你們精神都不錯啊
Well, don't you all look cheery.
聽聽這個
Listen to this...
今天薩賓在帶領游客參觀墓地時
A girl literally exploded from a grave today
一個女孩從墳墓里爬了出來
as Sabine was giving her tour of the city of the dead.
那個女孩是莫妮可·德弗羅
It was Monique Deveraux.
你說什么
What?
游客們還以為是安排的表演
The tourists thought it was part of the show,
但女巫們都認為這是奇跡
But the witches are celebrating
正在大肆慶祝呢
like it's some kind of bloody miracle.
誰說不是呢  她們本以為沒有希望了
Maybe it is. They think that all hope is lost,
可如今  一個收獲祭女孩突然就復活了
but now suddenly a harvest girl is resurrected.
或許我們也可以這樣救回達維娜
This is how we're gonna get Davina back--
殺死取代她位置的女巫
Kill the witch who took her place.
我或許知道那個人是誰
I have a theory about who one of them could be...
塞萊斯特  一定是她
Celeste. I mean, it's got to be.
達維娜之前就試著告訴我們
Davina was trying to tell us.
她畫了許多塞萊斯特的畫像
She was drawing pictures of celeste.
她是在提醒我們邪惡即將來臨
She was warning us that a great evil was coming.
先是圖德圣父回來找我們算舊賬
First Papa Tunde returns to settle old scores.
現在你那被我殺死的舊情人也回來了
Now your murdered lover is back.
這不是單純的女巫攻擊吸血鬼事件
This isn't witches attacking vampires.
她們是在向我們宣戰
They're declaring war on us.
現在喝酒不算早吧
It's not too early for scotch, is it,
畢竟我們要應付這一堆女巫的破事
With all the witches' shenanigans
還有一堆即將到來的陰謀詭計
and subterfuge afoot.
如果你一會要開車的話  那就不太合適了
It is entirely too early if one intends to drive, yes.
是嗎  但我可沒打算出去
Funny. I don't have any plans to go anywhere.
她留在這里不安全
She's not safe here.
你得將海莉帶到種植園去
You have to take Hayley to the plantation house
直到這一切結束
Until this is over.
你是在擔心海莉
Are you worried about Hayley
還是擔心你信不過我
or whether or not you can trust me?
正是因為信任你
It's precisely because I trust you
我會才請求你做這件事
that I'm asking you to do this.
我有個想法
Here's a novel idea--
何不讓海莉自己決定呢
why don't you let Hayley decide for herself?
為什么該由你決定她的命運
Why are you dictating her fate?
你知道的
You know why.
或許你該親自帶她離開
Then perhaps you should take her yourself.
如果這樣做  我就真的成為了
Well, then that would make me the very hypocrite
你口中所說的偽君子
that you've accused me of being.
麗貝卡  我無法克制自己的情感
Rebekah, I cannot legislate my feelings.
但我的行為則不同
My actions, however...
所以你能好心幫我這個忙嗎
So would you kindly do this for me?
你知道小母狼最不喜歡受人指使了
You know the mama wolf loves to be told what to do.
她不會喜歡的
She's not gonna like it,
但為了你我會這么做
But I will do it for you...
為了停止我們之間
If only to end this silly quarrel
這愚蠢的爭執
between the two of us.
你這是在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
聽著  大家都在四處搜索
Listen, everybody's running off,
尋找復活的女巫
looking for resurrected witches.
我想我在教堂見到了其中一個
Meanwhile, I think I saw one at the church...
杰妮薇
Genevieve.
你說什么
What?
我不確定
I can't be sure.
我只是無意中看到了她
I only caught her out of the corner of my eye.
之后我一直跟克勞斯在一起
Been with Klaus since.
但那個人看起來很像她
But it looked like her.
你我都知道她回來
And you and I both know she would have a reason
是有原因的
to want to be back.
那些多年前的舊賬
A lot of unfinished business,
那些你我都不希望被別人知道的秘密
A lot of secrets that you and I don't want getting out.
我現在要帶海莉去種植園
I have to take Hayley to the plantation.
你得找到杰妮薇  結束這一切
You need to find Genevieve and end this.
就像上次一樣
End it like we did the last time.
請給我杯茶
Tea, please.
我很忙
I'm busy.
卡米  聽我說完
Cami, just hear me out.
我去參加你的教堂重開儀式
You know, I came to your reopening
是因為我想試著去彌補
because I wanted to try and make amends.
然后我看到你大庭廣眾之下
And then I see you talking with Klaus
跟克勞斯交談
out in the open,
一副談論法屬區公事的樣子
like it's business as usual in the quarter.
確實是公事
It is business as usual.
三百多年來
For the past 3 centuries,
奧康納家的人一直在努力維護和平
the O'Connells have always tried to keep the peace.
別跟我扯家族歷史
Save me the family history.
謊話連篇
It's all lies on top of lies.
卡米  給  給我倒杯酒
Cami, p--pour me a drink.
我有事要跟你說
I have to tell you something.
基蘭叔叔  你怎么了
Uncle Kieran, what's wrong?
我有麻煩了
I'm in trouble.
曾發生在你兄弟肖恩身上的事
What happened to your brother Sean
要在我身上重演了
is about to start happening to me.
什么
What?
聽我說
Look, uh...
有人給我施了咒
Look, uh, I've been hexed.
我不知道我還剩多長時間
And I don't know how long I have.
等等  我認識一些人
Wait. I know some people.
肯定有辦法解決的  肯定會有
There has to be some sort of--I don't know--
解藥或者...
antidote or--
卡米  我要你向我保證一件事
Cami, I need you to promise me one thing,
一旦情況惡化
that when it gets bad,
你要離我越遠越好
I need you to be as far away from me as possible.
不  不要
No. No.
肯定會有辦法解決的
There has to be some sort of way.
當然有
Of course there is.
如果你想救你叔叔的命
If you want to save your uncle's life,
你只需要拿著這個
all you have to do is take this...
然后刺入克勞斯·邁克爾森的胸膛
and make sure it ends up in Klaus Mikaelson's heart.
我以為要讓你來這里
I thought I was gonna have to drag you
得使用一些暴力手段
to the plantation kicking and screaming.
是啊   可是我們都得保證寶寶的安全
Yeah. Well, we all just want to protect me and the baby,
對吧
right?
我是支持你的  記得嗎
I'm on your side, remember?
出什么事了
So what gives?
今晚是滿月  麗貝卡
Tonight's a full moon, Rebekah.
那又怎樣  你懷孕了  不能變身
So what? You're preggers. You can't turn.
對  但是我想邀請一些人
Yes. But I wanted to invite a few people over.
我懂了
Of course.
精力充沛的美國狼人在今晚
Every red-blooded american werewolf
都會變成獠牙尖利的野獸
will be a bundle of fur and sharp teeth tonight
而你們新月狼族受了詛咒
whilst your cursed crescent clan will be--
會變成人類  但只能維持幾小時
Human but only for a few hours
再變身只能在下個滿月之夜  所以...
and won't be again until the next full moon. So...
我讓喬什放出風聲給河口的伊芙
I asked Josh to get a message out to Eve in the bayou.
喬什還沒死嗎  真不錯
Josh isn't dead yet? Well, good on him.
真想聽聽他的驚險故事
I love a nice survival story.
那他媽是誰
Who the bloody hell is that?
啤酒桶在后面對吧
Kegs out back, right?
是的
Yep.
好
Right.
看來你沒有經過我的允許
It appears you weren't going to wait for me
就打算開一個啤酒聚會
to grant you permission to throw a kegger.
你們都希望我安全  沒問題
Listen, you all want me safe, fine.
我很聽話
I'll do as I'm told.
我可以做個溫室里的花朵
I'll play damsel in the glass tower.
但是每月只有今晚我才能見到家人
But tonight's the one night a month that I can meet my family.
你可以把我抓了  關回房間
Now, you could rat me out, send me to my room,
或者幫我舉辦一次
or you could help me throw
驚天動地的聚會
one hell of a party.
以利亞
Elijah.
你來找我有何貴干
To what do I owe the pleasure?
我家人需要一名女巫的幫助
My family needs an ally among the witches,
而你曾經幫助過我們
and you've helped us in the past.
也許我們可以一起
Perhaps together we can avoid
阻止一場不必要的爭端
an unnecessary conflict.
如果對象是高尚的以利亞
They may be willing to make a deal
她們可能很愿意合作
if it were with the noble Elijah.
但是只要牽扯到克勞斯
But there will never be any peace
就沒有任何和平可言
as long as it involves Klaus.
你就是為了這個嗎
Is that what all this is about?
你希望我弟弟離開這里
You want my brother out of town?
我只是告訴你她們的感受
I'm just telling you how they feel.
我的人很害怕  她們雖然絕望
My people are scared. They're desperate,
卻并不愚蠢
but they're not dumb.
如果牽扯到自己的侄女
You have a niece on the way.
誰都會開始考慮
It stands to reason you'd be willing to discuss
如何趕他離開
how to run him out of the city.
一起散個步吧
Let's walk together.
你可以帶我去參觀下那些著名景點
You can take me on one of your famous tours.
你多吃點
You should eat
經歷了那么多  一定餓了
after everything you've been through.
我死過一次
I was dead.
但是你現在活了
But you're here now.
索菲阿姨  媽媽怎么了
Aunt Sophie, what happened to mom?
你媽媽很愛你
Your mother loved you so much.
她堅信自己能夠用魔法
She had faith that she could use magic
完成收獲祭
to complete the harvest
并讓你復活
and get you back.
最后  她因此犧牲了
In the end, she sacrificed herself for the cause,
為了女巫們  為了你
for the witches, for you.
你也這樣相信嗎
And do you have her faith?
我失去了信仰
I lost my faith.
然后我意識到  如果我不相信
Then I realized that if I didn't believe,
一定會讓你失望
I would be letting you down.
我試過找回信仰  真的
I tried to get it back. I tried.
莫妮可·德弗羅
Monique Deveraux.
法屬區的人都在談論你
Everyone in the quarter's been talking about you.
真經典  你殺了她媽媽
Classy. You kill her mother
現在來威脅她了嗎
and now you've come to threaten her?
我來這里不是為了威脅
I'm not here to threaten anyone.
你想干什么  馬塞爾
What do you want, Marcel?
收獲祭還犧牲了另外三個女孩
There were 3 more girls sacrificed during the harvest.
我想讓她們復活
I want to bring them back.
你騙誰呢
Who are you kidding?
你根本不在乎那些女孩
You don't care about those girls.
你只是想讓達維娜復活  繼續利用她的魔力
You just want Davina back so you can use her power again.
我只是想讓她活著
I just want her alive.
他在說實話
He's telling the truth.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
我感覺得到
I can feel it.
他對她很忠誠
He's loyal to her.
他來這里是想幫忙
He's here to help.
收到你短信了
I got your message.
基蘭現在在哪里
Where's Kieran now?
他在閣樓休息  祈禱
In the attic resting, praying.
他會發瘋然后死亡  是吧
He's gonna go crazy and die, isn't he...
就像肖恩一樣
Just like Sean.
我還和他如此幼稚地吵架
And we'll still be in this stupid fight
因為他不告訴我女巫的事
because he lied to me about the witches
吸血鬼的事
and vampires...
你的事
and you.
卡米爾
Camille...
我明白你討厭我的原因
I can see why you hate me.
說實話  我干過很多殘忍的事
Truth be told, I have done some dreadful things.
但是你叔叔撒的謊  都是為了保護你
But the lies your uncle told were meant to protect you.
他是個好人
He is a good man...
心地善良
With a loyal heart.
他是你的家人
And he is your family.
至于那些女巫
As for these witches,
她們既然對基蘭下了手
their attack on Kieran should be proof enough
就說明是敵人
they're the enemy.
這一點我們一樣
In that we are united.
克勞斯
Klaus...
這是圖德圣父的匕首
This is papa Tunde's blade.
一個女巫給我的
A witch gave it to me.
說它可以造成無邊的痛苦
Said it would cause untold pain
哪怕對方是始祖吸血鬼
and torment, even to an original.
她說如果我刺進你的心臟
She said if I stuck it in your heart,
她就會治愈基蘭
she would heal Kieran.
而你選擇了拒絕她們的邀請
And yet you chose to reject their offer.
如果我更像你一點  應該會接受
Maybe if I were more like you, I could do it.
但我不...
But I'm not--
不是野獸
A monster.
我不蠢
I'm not stupid.
如果有戰爭要發生
If there's a war going on,
我希望站在贏的一邊
I want to be on the winning side.
來看看怎么救你的叔叔吧  好嗎
Let's see what we can do about saving your uncle, shall we?
你好
Hello again.
我很期待與你正式相見
I'm looking forward to meeting you soon.
你這是開玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
一個吸血鬼想要幫你
A vampire is trying to reverse
解除女巫施下的詛咒
a witch's hex placed on you,
而你卻覺得這杯子有瀆神靈
and it's the cup you find sacrilegious.
你確定這樣行得通嗎
Are you sure this is going to work?
我也不確定
Not remotely.
但是如果神父體內有馬鞭草
But I can't attempt to use my compulsion
我就不能使用意念控制
to counter Bastiana's curse if the good father
來對付巴斯蒂娜的咒語  所以
has vervain in his system. Thus...
要流光他的血
We bleed him out.
我從沒說過事情會很容易
I never said this would be pleasant.
你盡力做吧
Just do what you have to do.
我說到做到  馬塞爾  快回電話
So help me god, Marcel, if you don't call me
你再不告訴我情況  我就親手殺了你
back with an update, I will kill you myself.
不好意思
I beg... your pardon.
我以為客人會更毛茸茸一些
I was expecting someone furrier.
你是那類物種吧
You're one of them, aren't you?
始祖吸血鬼
An original.
對  你的語氣可以稍微尊敬一點
Yes. You might want to say that with some more respect.
你應該想見海莉吧
I suppose you'll be wanting Hayley.
或者我也可以跟你聊聊
Or I could just talk to you.
我叫奧利弗
I'm Oliver.
還不知道你叫什么
I didn't catch your name.
麗貝卡
I'm Rebekah.
海莉  參加派對的人來了
Hayley, the party's here!
你的能量還夠找到那些女巫嗎
You got enough power left to find these witches?
我知道收獲祭是個大失敗
I know the harvest was an epic fail,
不過我還有能力下個定位咒
but I can still do a locator spell.
在那之前
Before I do that,
我們得做個交易
we need to make a deal.
什么交易
What deal?
如果我背叛了這些女巫
If I betray these witches,
她們會來找我麻煩
they're gonna come looking for me.
如果我被抓住  我就死定了
and if I'm caught, I'm dead.
我說了我會保護你
I said I'd protect you.
如果你真能做得到
If you could do that,
一開始你也不會找我幫忙了
you wouldn't need my help in the first place.
法屬區危機四伏
The quarter isn't safe.
吸血鬼雄踞一方
Vampires on one side,
女巫與之對抗自成一派
witches on the other.
我絕不可能讓莫妮可陷入其中
No way am I letting Monique get in the middle of that.
為了帶她出去
In order to get her out,
我需要錢
I'm gonna need money.
成交嗎
Do we have a deal?
找到那些女巫  我給你想要的一切
Find the witches, I'll give you anything you could ever need.
來吧  你可以跳得更好的
Well, come on! You can do better than that.
對不起  今晚我太疲勞了
Sorry. I've got a burdened brain tonight.
不行不行
No, no, no, no.
今晚又不是用來加重負擔的
Tonight is not a night for burdens.
而是用來慶祝的
It's to celebrate.
享受我們短暫的歡慶時光
It's to enjoy life for the few hours that we get to live it.
我們要擁抱朋友  家人
It's to hug our friends, our family,
還要瘋狂的跳舞
and to dance our asses off.
真不敢相信你邀請我們來此
I seriously doubt you invited us here to wait on us.
你是海莉  我叫杰克遜
You're Hayley. I'm Jackson.
很高興又見面了
It's nice to see you again.
你就是那個監視我的狼人
You're the wolf who's been watching me.
我必須要盯著你
I got to keep my eye on you,
以及你體內的珍貴貨
precious cargo and all.
沒錯
Right.
必須保護這個奇跡般的孩子
Got to protect the miracle baby.
不  我不是這個意思
No. That's not what I meant.
我不在乎這個孩子
I don't care about the baby.
不對  那樣說不對
Sorry. That came out wrong.
我當然在乎孩子
I mean, of course I care.
你可是孕婦
You're a lab on air.
孩子  就是大事
A baby, it's a big deal.
但我個人的興趣  是你
But personally, my interest is in you.
你都不認識我
You don't even know me.
我們的父母互相熟識
Our parents knew each other.
他們是同一等級的人
They were of the same people
但不是同一血脈
but not the same bloodline.
你知道狼族等級制度是如何運作的吧
Now, you know how pack hierarchy works, right?
每個人都有設定好的角色
Everybody has their part to play,
我們也不例外
and we had our part, too.
我們的角色是什么
What part was that?
你應該成為我的妻子
You were supposed to be my wife.
下一個城區是為數不多的地區
So this next part of town is one of the few areas
仍然保留著最初的法國建筑
where any of the original french architecture remains.
大部分建筑在上個世紀70年代就被毀了
Most of the buildings were destroyed in the 1700s,
那時大火第一次吞噬了這座城市
when the city burned for the first time.
我說這些很無聊吧
Am I putting you to sleep?
你可能覺得驚訝
As surprising as you might find this,
并不是每天都有人
it's not every day that someone asks you
讓你背叛自己的兄弟
to betray your own brother...
塞萊斯特
Celeste.
你怎么發現的
How did you know?
達維娜畫出了你的樣子
As Davina was drawing your likeness,
我就大膽設想你就在附近
I dared to imagine that your presence was near.
然后索菲發現
And when Sophie discovered
在你的遺骸里沒有法力了
that there was no magic in your remains,
我便懷疑
I wondered...
你是不是有可能詐死
Could you have possibly cheated death by using
而將你的本體
your power to place your essence
置于另一具身體里
into the body of another?
如果是這樣  那么是誰
And if so, then who?
然后我回想起  可愛的薩賓
And then I recalled the lovely Sabine.
你還要繼續跟蹤我嗎  以利亞
Are you gonna continue following me, Elijah,
還是你想談談
or do you want to talk?
你知道我是誰
You know who I am.
永遠西裝革履的吸血鬼始祖
Original vampire, always wears a suit?
你看到的我弟弟孩子的幻象
Your visions of my brother's child
促成了女巫族群最后一位長者的死
precipitated the death of the last elder within your coven.
告訴他們你看到的
Tell them what you saw.
你要確保收獲祭
Ensuring that the harvest ritual
絕不能完成
could not be completed...
除非你能掌控它
unless you were to control it.
你真的下了很大的一盤棋
You're playing a very long game indeed...
為了什么
To what end?
以利亞
Oh, Elijah,
我失落的愛人
my lost love,
經過這么長時間
after all this time,
你還不明白嗎
don't you understand?
我因克勞斯而死
I died because of Klaus.
甚至在他為了報仇而對女巫說謊
And even after all his vindictive lies
導致我的死亡之后  你仍站在他那邊
about witches led to my death, you stood by him
只因你"永遠在一起"的誓言
all because of your vow, "Always and forever"
你對我做了什么
What have you done to me?
就是個簡單的法術
It's a simple enchantment.
不用擔心
You needn't worry.
我不是來殺你的  以利亞
I'm not here to kill you, Elijah.
我要讓你知道你的方式是錯的
I'm here to teach you the error of your ways.
"永遠在一起"是你一生最大的錯誤
"Always and forever" was the greatest mistake of your life.
喝了它
Drink up.
能治好你的傷
It will heal your wound.
我覺得你受的苦已經差不多了
I think you've suffered enough.
你會戰勝
You will overcome
女巫對你所做的一切
what the witches did to you.
你能抵抗她們的魔法帶來的黑暗沖動
You will resist the dark urges of their hex.
成功了嗎
Did it work?
我怎么知道成功了沒有
Ohh. How do I know if it worked?
我只知道我體內沒有馬鞭草了
All I know is that the vervain is out
只能任憑這個殺人魔擺布
and I'm at the mercy of this murderous bastard.
你一定覺得這很好笑對吧
I bet you find that really funny, don't you,
卡米  你這個小...
Cami, you little...
對不起
I'm--I'm sorry.
我不知道我為什么會說這些
I don't know why I said that.
好吧這就是答案了
Well, I guess that's our answer.
等等克勞斯  你要去哪里
Wait. Klaus, where are you going?
我們要做什么
What are we going to do?
我要去查出是哪個女巫干的
I'm going to find the witch who did this.
然后我就要做我最擅長的事
And then I'm going to do what I do best.
我要比預想的還要虛弱
I'm weaker than I thought.
你想要交易  索菲  那你就得遵守諾言
You want the deal, Soph, you got to hold up your end.
我時間緊迫
I'm on a clock.
好吧
Ok.
起作用了
It's working.
那才1個  我要3個
That's one. I need all 3.
我會把所有的結果都給你
I'm giving you whatever I can pick up.
繼續努力
Keep trying.
或者不用了
Or don't.
籌碼就在眼前
Who needs a locator spell
我還需要什么定位咒語呢
when I have all the leverage I need right here?
不  莫妮可
No! Monique!
你居然利用親我的時候下毒
You've poisoned me with a kiss.
看來你至少還沒失去諷刺感
Uh! At least you haven't lost your sense of irony.
我們也許還有時間享受更多呢
We may have time for more.
但首先  我要治愈的
But first, I'm going to cure you
是你最偉大的缺點  這種荒謬的
of your greatest flaw-- this absurd devotion
對瘋子般家人的奉獻
to your lunatic family.
我也和你一樣憤怒
Your anger is with me.
如果你是來復仇的
Now, if you have come here seeking revenge...
我會報仇的
Oh, I'll have my revenge,
從克勞斯開始
starting with Klaus.
他會了解前所未有的
He is gonna know pain and torment
痛苦與折磨
like he's never felt before...
除非你選擇要救他
Unless you choose to save him,
當然
of course.
但那就剩下了麗貝卡
But then that leaves Rebekah,
你可悲的妹妹
your tragic sister.
她會發現自己陷入了相當窘迫的狀況
She's about to find herself in quite the predicament.
你可以救她
You could save her.
但那樣海莉就危險了
But then that leaves Hayley in jeopardy.
不  不  不
No. No, no...
這個可憐的姑娘
Ah, this poor girl.
她完全不知道被你所愛是一件多危險的事情
She has no idea how dangerous it is to be loved by you.
當然
Oh, well.
你的身體被我的咒語所削弱
With your body weakened by my spell,
你不可能救下他們所有人
you won't be able to save them all.
你恢復后的時間只夠你選擇救一個人
You'll recover with just enough time to choose one.
會是誰呢
Who will it be?
真是迫不及待想知道呢
I can't wait to find out.
法屬區的女巫們
Witches of the French quarter,
我身邊這位是莫妮可·德弗羅
I have with me Monique Deveraux.
剛剛脫離死亡的她被我不得不
What a shame it would be were I forced to
再次殺死  真是太可惜了
send her back to the death she's just escaped.
你們希望不要發生這樣的情況
Should you wish to prevent this...
那就把女巫巴斯蒂娜給我找來
bring me the witch Bastiana.
你這是在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我在談判啊
I'm opening negotiations.
你知道我的規矩  我們不傷害孩子
You know my rules. We do not hurt kids.
省省你的虛偽的道德準則吧
Spare me the hypocrisy of your moral code.
那也沒能阻止你殺死莫妮可的媽媽
It didn't stop you from killing Monique's mother.
巴斯蒂娜  我知道你就在附近
Bastiana! I know you're close.
空氣里到處都是女巫的惡臭
The stench of witches hangs in the air.
記住我的話
Mark my words.
我要用你打算對付我的這把刀殺死這姑娘
I will end this girl with the very blade you meant for me.
我不會重復第二遍
I'm not saying it again.
我們不殺孩子
We do not kill kids.
在這里  由我決定誰生誰死  馬塞勒斯
I decide who lives and dies here, Marcellus.
下面我來處理吧
I'll take it from here.
我知道這很難接受
I know it's a lot to take in.
你覺得呢
You think?
我只是想見見我的家人
I just wanted to meet my family.
我從沒想過我會遇見我的丈夫
I never imagined I'd meet my husband
還是什么奇怪的包辦婚姻
from some weird-ass arranged marriage.
我想你不了解這些
I guess you don't know about any of this
因為從沒有人教過你
because there was never anyone around to teach you.
新月族人并不只是隨便的某一群狼
The crescents aren't just any pack of wolves.
這一脈血脈追溯到最開始
Ok? The bloodline goes back to the very beginning--
兩個家族  你的和我的
Two families-- yours and mine.
我想這就讓我們變得好像是皇室一樣了
I guess that makes us kind of like royalty.
這是玩笑吧
This is a joke, right?
如果你是皇室  你的王座在哪呢
I mean, if you're royalty, where's the throne?
新奧爾良曾經是我們的小鎮
New Orleans used to be our town.
我們在混戰中失去了它
And we lost it all because of some infighting.
吸血鬼追殺著我們
The vampires came after us.
如果我們的家族聯合起來  我們本能贏得戰爭
And if our families were united, we could have taken them.
所以我們的父母決定將兩個家族合并起來
So our parents decided to bring the two lines back together.
你和我就訂婚了
And you and I were betrothed.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
顯然事情并沒有像
Look, obviously things didn't work out
大家想得那樣發展
the way anyone thought they would.
我們狼群犯了一個巨大的錯誤
Our pack made a huge misstep with the vampires
我們拒絕對吸血鬼妥協
when we refused to back down.
馬塞爾就讓女巫給我們下了咒
And Marcel had us cursed by a witch.
你是你家族血脈的最后一個人了  安卓利亞
You are the last one of your bloodline, Andrea.
或是海莉  不管你怎么稱呼自己
Or, Hayley, whatever you call yourself.
這些人會跟著你
These people will follow you.
你可以幫助他們  你以及你所代表的
You can help them--you and what you represent.
那到底是什么呢
And what is that exactly?
一切還是不同的時候
A time when things were different,
我們的種族還在抗爭的時候
when our people fought back.
在你經歷了一切找到我們之后
And after everything you went through to find us...
你是唯一能打破詛咒的人
You're the one who's gonna break our curse.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你的女巫朋友
Your witch friend.
她告訴伊芙她今晚會來解除我們的咒語
She told Eve she was coming here tonight to set us free.
等下  什么女巫朋友
Wait. What witch friend?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很喜歡你  但這是我們早已達成的協議
I really do like you, but this is the deal we made.
什么協議
What deal?
和誰
With whom?
[咒語]
海莉
Hayley.
以利亞  女巫們在謀劃著什么
Elijah, something's going on with the witches.
聽我說  你說的沒錯
Listen to me. You were right.
塞萊斯特回來了
Celeste is back.
尼克勞斯  麗貝卡  你們都處在危險之中
Niklaus, Rebekah. You're all in danger.
怎么回事
What's going on?
這是個陷阱  我從沒和女巫達成過協議
It's a trap. I didn't make a deal with any witch.
-什么  -海莉  你得找到麗貝卡
- What? - Hayley, you have to find Rsebekah.
在我到之前和她待在一起
And you stay with her until I get there.
以利亞  這是個咒語
Elijah, it's a spell.
我們被困在屋內了
They're trapping us inside.
[咒語]
你知道怎么做
You know what to do.
我們得離開這里
We have to get out of here.
給  透過這個呼吸
Here. Breathe through this.
麗貝卡呢
Where's Rebekah?
不知道
I don't know.
她和他們中的一個人出去了
She went off with one of them.
以利亞  我朋友還在里面
Elijah, my friend is still in there.
站起來
On your feet.
救命
Help me.
已經過了這么久了  麗貝卡
It's been such a long time, Rebekah.
我會很享受這過程的
I'm going to enjoy this.
少了什么嗎
Missing something?
你不會傷害我的
You won't hurt me.
我是唯一活著能打破
I'm the only one alive who can break
海莉家族詛咒的人
the curse on Hayley's family.
而杰妮薇知道你妹妹在哪
And Genevieve knows where your sister is.
巴斯蒂娜把克勞斯藏在了一個安全的地方
Bastiana has Klaus tucked away someplace safe.
我得說一句  他正在痛苦煎熬
He's suffering horribly, I might add,
那都是因為你選擇去救
and all because you chose to save
那只小狼女而不是你的家人
the little wolf instead of your own blood.
多么可怕的結局
What a horrific ending...
對你的可悲的病態的家族來說
to your pathetic, diseased family.
我想"一直"終究不會是永遠
I guess "always" isn't forever after all.
我得走了  月亮
I have to go. The moon.
聽著  杰克遜
Listen, Jackson,
我想謝謝你保護我
I want to thank you for protecting me,
不只是今晚
not just tonight.
我從孩童時  就一直幻想著我們的見面
I've been dreaming about meeting , since I was a kid.
我從沒想過會變成這樣
I never thought it would go like this.
我不會停止尋找辦法打破詛咒
I won't stop until I find a way to break this curse.
我保證
I promise.
快點  快點  快點接啊
Come on. Come on. Come on.
克勞斯  你在哪
Klaus, where are you?
邁克爾森先生現在正身體不適
Mr. Mikaelson is currently indisposed.
怎么了  你做了什么
What happened? What did you do?
什么都沒做
I did nothing.
有人替你完成了你的任務
Someone completed your task for you.
如果你得到了你想要的  那我叔叔
If you got what you wanted, then my uncle--
很快就會死去  并且會極其痛苦
Will die soon and in great anguish.
你瞧  親愛的  你沒能遵守我們的諾言
You see, dear, you failed to hold up your end of our bargain.
你叔叔多次與邪惡為友
You chose instead to side with evil as your uncle
而你也同他一樣
has done many times before you.
不過  振作點
But take heart.
他的懲罰將會彌補他數次嘗試
His punishment will atone for his attempts
阻止收獲祭
to prevent the harvest.
他的痛苦將會凈化他
His suffering will purify him.
你吸取他的教訓就會做得更好了
You'd do well to heed his lesson, girl.
與我們作對就是與自然秩序作對
To oppose us is to oppose the natural order.
選擇或被迫
By choice or by force,
法屬區的女巫們將會再次崛起
the witches of the french quarter will rise again.
我們到處找了
We looked everywhere for him.
把女巫區  墓地  翻了個底朝天
Tore apart the cauldron, the city of the dead.
他們關他的地方肯定不在法屬區
Wherever they got him, he ain't in the quarter.
馬塞爾
Marcel!
我弟弟在哪
Where is my brother?
我的人正在外面找他
I got guys out looking for him right now.
以利亞
Elijah!
克勞斯又沖我發脾氣了
Klaus threw one of his classic temper tantrums,
扭斷了我的脖子
snapped my neck,
試圖獨自一人與一群女巫較量
tried to take on a coven of witches by himself.
他被控制了
He got dropped.
我不知道他在哪  也不知道怎么找到他
I don't know where he is or how to find him.
他們還抓走了麗貝卡
They also have Rebekah.
在場的每一個人都要幫助我找到他們
Every one of you will help me to find them.
我要把他們都殺光
I'm going to kill them all.
來  我們得走了
Come on. We have to go.
我不想走
I don't want to go.
莫妮可  這不是討論
Monique, this isn't a debate.
我剛剛捅了一個始祖
I just stabbed an original.
他一旦恢復就會殺了我的
He's gonna kill me as soon as he's recovered.
聽著
Look...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry for everything.
我應該在那個愚蠢的收獲祭前
I should have come and got you
就來找你
before that stupid harvest.
但你還是可以擁有正常的生活
But you can still have a normal life,
沒有這些女巫什么的生活
one without all this crazy witch nonsense.
但我就是女巫
But I am a witch.
我不想走
And I don't want to go.
莫妮可
Monique?
祖先們說你沒有足夠的信仰
The ancestors said you didn't have enough faith.
我本希望是他們錯了
I was hoping they were wrong.
我早就該知道的
I should have known better.
莫妮可
Monique...
你試圖阻止收獲祭
You tried to stop the harvest.
求你不要這么做
Please don't do this.
現在在我們需要留下來戰斗時  你想逃走
Now you want to run when we need to stay and fight.
求你了  求求你  不要
Please. I'm begging you, don't--don't--
我們四個人  我們死而復生時
The four of us, when we return,
我們就有足夠的法力能夠清理這里的吸血鬼
we'll have enough power to rid the city of vampires,
我們會殺死每一個
and we'll kill anyone...
沒有足夠信念的人
who doesn't keep the faith.
莫妮可
Monique...
求你了
Please...
你應該相信的
You should have believed.
住手  求你了
Stop. Please.